

CONTACT ME AT

• Noida, Uttar Pradesh

drishtibahl68@gmail.com

(+91) 8800401109

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/drishti-bahl-37a487196/

https://github.com/drishtibahl12

DIGITAL PORTFOLIO - https://drishtibahl12.github.io/MyPortfolio/

SKILLS

- Public Relations
- Communication
- Team Player
- Kali Linux
- Wireshark
- Nmap
- HTML5 &CSS3
- Network Security
- Nessus tool

CERTIFICATIONS

- CEH v11 by EC-Council Ongoing
- Security+ by CompTIA Ongoing
- Cyberops Associate by
 Cisco Networking Academy
- HackNU 3.0 by NIIT University

PROJECTS

Password cracking

Impact of Video Knowledge base (R&D Project)

CRUD Application

Evolution from 5G to 6G

DRISHTI BAHL

CYBERSECURITY GRADUATE

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a passionate Computer Science student at NIIT University. My research and career interests lie at the nexus of Cybersecurity and Networking. Enthusiastic and dedicated to my work in the field of management and networking. Determined to be an asset.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cybersecurity Analyst Intern

Craw Security | Jan 2022 - April 2022

- Learnt about the identification of cyber security solutions with respect to different attacks.
- Learnt about the implementation of the solution in real time world.
- Gained a good knowledge about basics of Networking and Security.

Interned at Cisco

Cisco Networking Academy | April 2021 - Sept 2021

- Polished my Cybersecurity Skills like Nmap Scanning, Wireshark, System Hacking, Vulnerability Analysis
- Learnt the fundamentals of Networking and performed certain tasks in practical scenario.
- Learnt about the Packet Tracer software and built basic network structure.

Head of Public Relations at Sinusoid

NIIT University Tech-Fest | 1st Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

- Plan, Develop and execute the publicity and brand establishment strategies.
- Introduced the Fest Ambassador program in order to build strong networking for the fest.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

NIIT University - Specialisation: Cybersecurity

Bachelors of Technology - Computer Science & Engineering | C.G.P.A.: 7.31 | Aug 2019 - May 2023

Ahlcon Public School (XII) - Science(Non-Medical)

C.B.S.E. | **Secured: 94.8**% | April 2018 - March 2019

The Khaitan School (X) - Secondary

C.B.S.E. | **Secured:** 9.8/10.0 | April 2016 - March 2017

POSITION OF RESPONSIBILITY

- Buddy Mentor in NanoEPL, NIIT University
- SPOC at TedXNIITUniversity
- Public Relations Head at Sinusoid